Good evening.
We just finished our respective jobs.
The three of us are having dinner and filming for YouTube.
This is how we did it.
Today, we're going to take it easy.
Yes, I'd like to do that.
We're going to be relaxed.
We ordered a meal from UberEats a while ago.
I'm looking forward to it!
And here's the plan for today.
Let's see!
Please show me!
I'm so happy!
Ta-da!
We're going to play the game of life!
Yay!
My family used to play this all the time.
It was in the house.
We had the exact same one at home.
That could be awesome.
Yeah, it is.
Oh, my God.
I know, right?
I used to be a dongara.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to do Dongara next time.
Let's do it.
I can do it just a little bit.
Just a little bit.
That was once!
Let's play the game of life today.
Let's play!
Yes, let's do it.
Let's do it! Let's do it! Let's do it!
Let the game of life begin!
Yay!
Yes, this is it.
First of all, let's take turns.
That's right.
I have to decide.
Yes, yes, yes.
Since we have roulette...
Biggest number first.
That's enough.
Let's do it.
Okay, I'll go with Amirai.
Here we go!
I'll turn it.
It's not so bad.
It's fun.
Oh, wait.
Three.
I got a 30% one.
I got one.
That's right.
Yes, sir.
Four! Let's go!
Here we go!
Which way should I look?
8! So...
Ogi's first, Sayumi's second.
And me...
I'm number 3! Yes!
So, car insurance
I want to get in!
Thank you!
This is the first one.
The more you have, the better.
Later on, the more important people
I can help you. I can help you, so...
Please start with Ogi-chan!
Start!
Very nice, all around!
5!
Which way are you going? White car for you, Ogi-chan.
I'm going to the business course.
Or the professional course.
Professional?
Oh, profession.
One, two, three, four.
Five!
I could be a celebrity!
$12,000 salary.
Take the profession card.
Go to square one! What do you do?
I like it!
I'll be a TV personality again!
You know, I could stay in a better square.
I might be able to stay in a better one.
But by the time I get here.
If you stay here.
I'll get used to it.
I see.
If I put out more than 8 squares...
I'm a freelancer!
I'm a TV personality!
I'll go 8 squares.
When's your payday?
$5,000.
I can get you life insurance.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir!
Always.
$12,000. 12,000 yen
Ori-chan's life insurance policy.
Ta-da!
Let's get a life insurance policy!
Life insurance is important.
Okay, let's go!
Yes!
Eight!
I'm going to the professional course.
Good luck.
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Oh! Yes!
Oh, no!
You're a researcher!
What?
I can be a researcher!
20,000 yen salary.
If you like, you can get a profession card.
50,000 yen.
Yes!
I want to be a researcher!
Researcher!
I'll be a researcher!
Let's go.
You want to come in with me?
I'm in!
Five thousand, right?
Five thousand. Five thousand.
Okay, 5,000.
Oh, I'm out.
Hey, thank you.
I got life insurance.
Yay!
Okay, everyone, my turn.
I'm going to the professional course.
Oh!
Eighth and sixth.
Oh! Oh!
Oh, 10!
Here we go!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I can be a video creator.
10,000 yen salary.
It's the cheapest.
Sure, sure, sure.
Compared to three
Well, I'll become one.
I'll do it.
Join a professional course?
I'm in!
Okay, 5,000. 5,000.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Video.
No, but this is a doggie.
Yeah. - Yeah.
If you rank up, you'll get a video.
No, I mean, yeah.
This could be bad.
Here you go.
I'll turn it.
I'll start from here.
That's right.
Mochi mochi mochi!
Five.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
I got through karaoke without memorizing the lyrics.
I'll take $10,000.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
I did it!
That's amazing.
Yay! Yay!
I'm not good at memorizing lyrics
Yay!
I love it!
Okay, I'll go.
Okay, I'm going.
Oh! There it is! It's going so fast.
We've got to get to the finish line.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Oh, there he is.
I'll pay you 3,000 yen for waking up to skin care.
I'll pay you 3,000 yen.
2,000 yen? Next.
It's important to take care of your skin.
It's important.
Okay, then.
Okay, I'm off.
Why are you blurting out?
Nine!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
What? We did it!
That's great.
I'll show a lost backpacker the way.
I get $20,000.
Oh, that's great!
I'm going into business!
Ori-chan
6!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Marriage?
If I get 1,3,5,7,9, I'm not getting married.
2,4,6,8,10.
You and Ruth kiss.
I'll marry you.
I'm going. Here we go.
To marry or not to marry? Or not?
Ah...
Sookhee... Sookhee...
Sookhee!
I'm not getting married!
I'm not married!
Single!
You're single!
Okay, here I go.
Suka na...
Oh, yes, yes, stop.
Stop, right?
So, shall we go?
Fate's fork in the road
Ah!
10!
I'm getting married!
Marriage!
Married?
I have to say it one more time.
It's just the two of us!
We're two!
We're on a course for six.
All right, let's go.
I guess we're still stopping.
Yes, stop.
Stop, five squares.
Here we go.
I'll line you two up.
One of you...
Nakomi, Nakohama.
And I'm, well, I'm just one more person, so I'll go with Machi.
Oh!
I'll go with Machi.
Town
I'll call you Machi.
Oh! Ooh.
Quiet.
In the fullness of space.
Uh, which one is it?
Three?
Not three?
Uh...
One, two, three.
I don't know how to register for subs.
I'll pay you $10,000.
Uh-oh.
I understand
I understand.
Uh...
It's falling apart.
Payday.
Payday?
Payday
12,000 yen.
Then you're only getting $2,000.
You can buy up to two stock certificates at $3,000 a piece.
Do you want to buy?
I'll buy them.
Oh, I'll buy two.
Oh, yes.
That's $6,000.
Six thousand dollars.
Okay, here we go.
I see.
So once you touch the payday...
So it's mandatory payday.
Eight.
Okay, well...
But I'm going to go to the woods. But I'll go to the forest.
Yes, sir.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, I did it, I did it, I did it
The sunrise from the mountains washed over me... and I got my $30,000.
I'll take $30,000. I'm washed up.
That's great.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, so that's $50,000.
That's right.
Plus salary.
So...
I'd like to buy two stock certificates.
You want to buy?
I'll buy them.
You're annoying me.
It's annoying.
Come on.
Mr. Bank.
Here I go!
Wait a minute.
Cue me. I'll go for the march course.
I knew it. First one goes to the march course.
Seven, eight, nine.
I'm impressed by the street musician's song.
I'll give you $1,000.
You want to buy a relationship?
I'll buy it.
Then I'll pay you 6,000 yen and 1,000 yen, that's 3,000 yen.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
OK.
Let's go.
Go.
Five times for life.
One, two, three, four, five.
I got a locked wallet, I got $8,000!I found your locked wallet!
Congratulations!
I'll take the $8,000.
I'm so happy for you.
Let's go, let's go!
I'm good. I can't get athletic video.
I'm taking a break.
What, are you a videostreamer?
What?
More like a researcher.
One break.
Okay, let's go.
That way, that way, that way.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
I'll pay you $1,000 to use our agency.
I don't know how to register for subscriptions... and it's 10,000 yen...
I'm sure...
I'm a coursekeeper, it's $1,000.
Thank you very much.
What do you mean?
I'm in.
Come on.
Come on, 10. 10.
Ten.
Four and five for life.
That's great.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Yes!
ee-ee
yes
Yes!
yes!
yeah yeah yeah
yes, yes, yes! yeah!
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Let's see what's coming up.
That's a lot of progress.
Oh, Kilby.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Seven.
Um, you want to go to the woods?
I paid $2,000 for it, and the way the arrow sticks is great.
I'm going to the forest.
Yes, I paid 2,000 yen.
I'll give you 9,000 yen.
Oh, and, plus, do you want fire insurance?
I'm in.
That's 3,000 yen.
Oh, again.
You haven't even bought a house yet.
You haven't even bought a house yet. Hey.
Oh, 8
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8
200 emails super-powerful.
Hey, you know, something like this...
There are a lot of cell phones like that.
I'll pay 10,000 yen again.
200 e-mails shut off with super strong security.
Oh, it's important, right?
2,000 yen for a label.
Oh, salary.
Oh, I see.
Insurance?
No.
You don't?
I live alone, so I guess it's okay.
Oh, well...
Bon appétit.
Let's see what we got.
Oh, nine!
It's rolling back. It's rolling back.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
Oh! Oh, no!
My house is actually a power spot.
I got $25,000.
Yes! I can't tell you yet.
I can't say for sure.
Yay!
It's a power spot.
What's that? Payday?
No, it's not payday yet.
Payday grafiken.
I want $15,000 for 20 grand.
I'll get you fire insurance.
Okay, that's fine.
You know, the way I'm looking at it, we're going to need fire insurance. You know, you're gonna need fire insurance.
What? I have fire insurance.
I've got it. I've got it.
I told you my course.
Yes!
Oh, I see it.
Yes, sir! I'll turn it.
It's out!
I saw it.
It's coming out so fast!
You can see it, right?
That's one, right?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I'm sure! I'm sure!
Rank-up payday
When you spin the set and get the number on the food card...
Swap the cards and move up the ranks.
You also choose the payday for the food.
Oh!
If you get a number between 3 and 10, you're up in rank.
Isn't this a huge area? Range
Yeah, but maybe they're all the same.
They're popping up. They're popping up.
One, two, zero.
Here we go!
Pounding, pounding, pounding.
Aaaaah!
I've become a very popular video creator!
It's expensive.
50,000?
Fifty thousand.
Fifty thousand dollars.
Yes, sir.
No, no, no, no.
Yes, $50,000. Yes, sir. $50,000.
Thank you, $50,000.
Hey.
That's great.
I'm so happy.
That's a lot of money.
That's it!
I'm going to be the top in Japan.
Well then...
O-chan
Yes, ma'am.
I have the best favor to ask.
Yes.
Fifty thousand dollars.
The timing is perfect.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I can be a full recording lawyer for illegal races.
eh?
What? I can change this.
Yes, you can.
I can change my profession.
What?
Yes, you can!
Lawyer. Lawyer.
Lawyer
20,000 kills
I don't know...
I don't know about illegal race.
Next 20,000.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
My lawyer.
Uh...
How much? how much?
expensive!
60,000 for a lawyer?
That's not good!
Right?
Hey...
That's what you were saying.
Yes.
Please don't stop.
That's right.
Let's go!
It's Roppo!
Yes, sir.
Five.
Is it over?
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, no.
$1,000 to buy the kinugiri gems.
Ahh.
You wanted a drink.
I bet you went down to the city.
Yeah, I did.
I'd like my change.
I wonder who has the most now.
Saya has the most.
Yay!
Thank you.
Here you go.
Mia!
Yes, ma'am.
I'll turn it.
It's Miria.
Wow, it's going so fast!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
I've got my paycheck!
I was able to make professional quality soba! I was able to make professional quality soba noodles.
I'll take $30,000. That's great. $30,000 plus.
Fifty thousand.
Plus stocks, stocks, stocks.
Sixty thousand. Six thousand.
Six thousand dollars.
You know, the points game's been strong for two years.
Yes, it is.
No, no, no. We have money. The last one.
Yes, the last one. It's pretty good.
Yes, that's right.
It's big, isn't it? Yes, it is.
I only get 5 to 6 for the rest of my life.
One minute.
Congratulations. One more?
Yes, one, two...
One, two is good for death.
Here we go.
Come on, come on, come on. Congratulations. Congratulations.
Congratulations. - Yay!
What does it say? I'm an international lawyer.
That's hot. That's great. You're out of Japan.
I'm going.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
One by one, please.
Five, yes.
Oh, yay!
Chunk it up.
Forty-five thousand.
Dr. Brennan: Dr. Brennan.
Congratulations.
I'm Dr. Seiyan.
So far away. So far away.
Then, Yumetan...
You're totally full of it.
Is it a stop? Stops?
One, two, three, four, five.
Stop.
All players play rock-paper-scissors-paper
The winner is
The winner
You can get one treasure of your choice from the extra squares on the field.
It was decided to use the Treasure Challenge squares.
Treasure
There are so many treasures in the field!
Whoever wins in a game of rock-paper-scissors
You have a chance!
You have a chance.
First, goo. Rock, paper, scissors.
First, goo, then rock, paper, scissors.
It's Aiko, right? It's Aiko, right?
I win.
Does it matter?
Really?
I don't care if it's cheap.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's easy to do on the cheap.
Keep it.
Yes, I'm a...
A camper.
$150,000 for a camper.
Oh, no.
So... what's it gonna be, in the end?
I don't know.
When you do the math.
You get it in the calculations.
I see.
That makes you happy?
I'm happy.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
But this one, too.
I'm still working on it. I'm still working on it.
I have a request.
All right. - All right.
Here we go.
All right.
Okay.
Oh, nine!
Two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine!
Oh, it's Cub Cubby.
Cub Cubby.
I'm buying!
Okay.
Bon appétit!
What can I drink?
Oh! That's a big one!
How much?
Uh, four.
Do you want to buy it?
I'll buy it.
Okay, so, grade 3?
Grade 3!
Nobody bought a house.
No one bought a house!
I see a house.
I'm sure.
Oh, these are all properties.
See, because here...
There's the Pigeon Hotel.
The Pigeon Hotel?
The last of the properties.
You get paid a lot of money for production.
I like it. I love it.
Yes.
I buy a house.
We've got kids and stuff.
I'm not welcoming anyone. I didn't welcome anyone.
No one picked up.
Ew.
I've been wanting to get my hands on one of these for quite a while now.
Maybe.
Seven.
Not a big number.
Two, three, four, five, six, seven.
What, what, what, what?
Oh, they're giving away the treasure. The treasure.
What? Where's the treasure?
I have extra money.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God!
That's what I'm talking about!
I've been saved by a luxury watch.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
Yes!
Then I hope you don't go away.
I won't.
Come on.
One, two, three.
I get two stock certificates with better rights.
Yay.
Yay!
Stock certificates all over the place!
Yay share certificates!
Okay, I'm going!
Six.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Oh...
You're remodeling the house?
Oh! That's great!
That's great!
The remodeling money made it.
How was it?
Oh! OH!!!
It has arrived!
Aah! Yay!
Thank you!
Yay! I'm so happy!
Just drinks!
We've got more coming in!
Thanks for your hard work!
Thank you so much!
We're all together.
Yes!
We ordered matching tapioca!
Matching tapioca!
So cute!
Panda Strawberry and
This is Roland's!
Yay!
That's great!
What's that? When did I order this?
I'm sure.
Oh, no.
Huh?
Ah! Oh!
It's from the staff.
Borrow it.
Oh, my God! Great!
Let's do it!
Money doughnuts are delicious.
Aah! What? Huh? Huh?
Over here.
You know, the one that looks like a staff member.
No, I just picked this out myself.
Why did you do this cute little herb, too?
You picked them yourself, didn't you?
and
Main dish
Pizza! Pizzazz!
Yay!
I'm so happy for you.
Here you go.
What?
You know what?
This is it.
Flass.
What?
Huh?
So we're doing two projects right now.
Are you eating?
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yum!
Bon appétit!
Yum.
Delicious.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Can I have some? Yeah. - Yeah.
Didn't you say something earlier? What? What?
Now that we've all eaten our fill, I'd like to resume the life gag.
What? Is there something going on? Who are you talking about? What?
First of all... Fessner!
Oh, my God! Fesner! Fesner!
Oh, my God! I chose him! I want to do Miri's.
Look out! Watch out! From Jaamiri
Thank you for watching! Thank you for watching!
Rockin' here!!!
You don't have it yet.
First, rock-paper-scissors-poi!
I got Hirotan's car.
Sei-chan is dominating everything in that staff cell.
Oh, man, rock, paper, scissors team.
Don't they burn the treasure cards?
Yes!
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes!
Thank you, Ogi-chan.
Why?
It's the most expensive. Digital art.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'll take this digital art.
Thank you, Ogi.
Last one.
Sorry about that.
Did you get it? Yes!
It's the same one you're holding.
Five.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll pay you $40,000 for laughing out loud and losing my voice.
You don't have to pay that much.
Wait a minute.
That's it!
Yes!
Eight!
Oh, I'll go on.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Oh, you're coming on the ninth?
I'll buy a pure white horse for $30,000.
Nine days!
Nine days of the week, I get $35,000. You get $35,000 for nine days.
That's right.
It takes more than a pure white horse to give me a voice.
I'm looking forward to it.
Here we go!
Thank you for watching.
Oh, no! Ichi!
My child is getting married, and everyone is over there!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
I read that they are proud of it.
I'm sure you'll have a baby, too.
Thank you very much!
I'm in!
The kids are over there, no matter who's staying there.
Ichi!
That's unusual.
The kid's auditioning for the show.
Okay, I'll turn it around.
The kid's not here, guys.
I don't have any.
Seven!
One, two, three, four, five, stamp!
Oh, I don't know, when did that happen?
It's true.
I left it!
Yes!
It says "Yay!" on it.
Settlement day
You get 3 cards for each passenger other than yourself.
There is only one.
None.
Return one promissory note for $25,000.
No one has a promissory note.
If there is no promissory note
All right, now.
Here's how we're going to do it.
Hmm. Nothing. Nope, nothing.
The end.
There is none.
There was nothing to settle.
He asked for something like three people, three years old, one vacation.
Wait.
Okay, then.
Let's go.
Five.
Two.
One.
2 2
2 2 2
Nine. 9
I don't have any food.
I can't get Saya to eat this.
That's right!
Hexagon
One.
Two, three, four, five, six.
Oh, I knew it was bad.
I'm having a home party with Rip.
I'll pay him $30,000.
I keep paying him $30,000.
I don't get paid at all. I'm sad.
I don't have any money.
Here we go.
I hope this check is at the finish line.
Seven.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Children.
No, sir.
I'll see you then.
I'll get $100,000 to leave my name on the wrestlers for developing new energy!
Thank you very much.
Lately, I've been into space. New energy development.
100,000.
Yay!
I'll get $100,000 to leave my name on the wrestlers for developing new energy!
Oh!
Oh, I turned it.
It's going around, around, around.
What's that? Shall we go back in time?
Yeah, you're right.
Sorry. Sorry.
This is life.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize.
Oh, something. Oh, something.
Goal.
Eh, so
Goal
Goal.
Oh, goal!
Sorry, sorry.
Bucky!
We did it!
We have reached the goal!
Risa came in first!
Coordination
It's over 100,000 yen!
I don't even know I did it!
That was good.
It was good, wasn't it?
What's the goal?
Huh?
And I've got it.
With one Kabukin.
$10,000.
Pops, I'll start next turn.
The finishers.
Whenever it's your turn
I turn the roulette.
And if you get an eight...
You get $20,000.
Oh!
What's that?
That's right.
That's what I'm talking about.
Slow down.
Turn.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
All but 1 and 2 for now.
Uh, seven. Oh, seven.
Wait a minute.
We've scored a goal.
We're in second place.
50,000 yen.
I'll take it.
Fifty thousand dollars.
For those of you with sugar in your head.
I don't know about you, but I'll tell you what.
I'll take the $50,000, please.
Kabukin.
Kabukin Kabukin.
Four Kabukins, so...
Forty thousand dollars.
I'll take $40,000, please.
I'll have five.
Yes, sir.
Uh...
What was that?
Yes, one.
Here we go.
Your life is not over.
My life is not over.
Two girls.
Four.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
One, two, three.
Oh, my gosh!
I did it!
From my female mentor.
I got something for you.
I'll take $50,000.
Yay.
Thank you very much.
Hey, guys, wait up.
You're rich. You're rich.
Oh, I'm scared.
This place.
I haven't been there yet.
Shall we go?
I'm in.
Three, two, one.
Eight.
Six.
Seven. One.
One.
Five.
I can't do it in five. Oh, no, no, no.
One, two, three, four, five.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I can't get on CNN. I can't get on CNN.
I don't know why...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
That's Dr. Brennan.
Dr. Bishop. Dr. Bishop.
Eight.
Here we go.
Nice try.
Seven.
-
So, I don't play the game of life.
If there is, I'd like to move on to production.
Thank you for watching.
Let's hear it from the princess.
Seven for $381,000.
Oh, wow.
Well done, sir.
I lied.
I'm sorry. That was $351,000.
Thirty-seven thousand.
That was 390,000.
Three hundred and ninety thousand.390,000
Oh, I was wrong.
One, two, three, four, five.
Four hundred and ten thousand dollars.
$401,000.
Yes, sir.
Good night.
May I?
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Wrong number, White.
$578,000.
We have some treasures.
We have $110,000 for the flying car and $150,000 for the camper.
Plus $260,000.
Tecoto is...
$38,000.
That's over 20,000.
You should lock him up too, Mie.
I've got two treasure cards I'd like to exchange for money.
$120,000 for a high-end electronic watch.
$100,000 for the digital art.
$220,000.
Cute.
One, two, three, four, five.
Fifty.
Fifty-five.
That's $628,000.
Ooh. Oh!
Tekoto is the
The winner is
Sayaya
It was a good life
Thank you.
It's been a good life.
I'm so happy.
But, you know, I came in third.
I felt like I was going through the second half of the race.
It was amazing!
So today was a lot of fun with UberEats and the game of life!
It was fun.
This is fun, isn't it?
I hope we can do another game project or UberEats project.
Let's do it!
I want to play DONJARASHI
Let's do DONJALASHI!
The second one.
Yeah, the second one, too.
I hope we can do it.
Well, thank you all for watching.
Bye-bye.
See you soon.